Then let the evidence speak
Since Miss Su wants to talk about evidence
Gu Group also prepared project progress records
First prove I was informed
Then prove I agreed
Finally claim I'm not responsible
The sequence is perfect
Miss Su
Did you send this email yourself
It's from Miss Su's personal email
Gu Group has reason to believe she
Was aware and agreed to proceed
Hmph
You say that so smoothly, Mr Gu
Did you think seeing
This email would make me panic
I attended the preliminary meeting
But I never agreed to expand the guarantee scope
Can I connect to the big screen
Connect it
Mr Gu
Does cropping out the prerequisites
Count as stating facts
The current guarantee scope is limited to
Yunwan Phase 1 construction funds